Register of the Vrangel' collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- PHOTOGRAPHS (Boxes 169-170, 170A, 171-175, 175A)
  - P.W. 2 (Box 174)
    - Photographs and clippings of photographs from newspapers related to material in P.W. 2
      Photographs for the "Notes of General Baron Petr Nikolaevich Wrangel," related to Baron P. Vrangel's memoirs, Beloe Delo. 80 items.
  - P.W. 9
    - Album: "Donskoi Korpus svoemu Glavnokomanduiushchemu v Pamiat' Prebyvaniia na o. Lemnose,", 1920-1921
      Presented to Baron P. Vrangel' by Don Cossack Corps.
  - P.W. 10
    - Album: "Tersko-Astrakhanskii kazachii polk za-granitsei,", 1925
      Presented to Baron P. Vrangel' by Regiment of Terek-Astrakhan Cossacks.
  - P.W. 11 (Box 175)
    - Album: "Glavnokomanduiushchemu i Pochetnomu Predsedateliu Obshchestva, Zagrebskii Otdel Gallipoliitsev, 17-X-26,", undated
      In leather case. Also includes typescript essay by M. Gonero, "CHetyrnadtsat' mesiatsev na serbskoi pogranichnoi sluzhbe," and map indicating disposition of contingents.
  - P.W. 12
    - Album: "Pskovskie Leib Draguny, Mitavskie Gusary i SHtab 2-oi Kav. Brigady Svoemu Orlu Vozhdiu-Glavnokomanduiushchemu Russkoi Armii Generalu Baronu P.N. Vrangeliu podnosit vospominanie o sluzhbe v 20-oi chete IV odseka Pogranichnoi Strazhi Korolevstva S.KH.S.,", 1921-1922
      Photographs and drawings.
  - P.W. 13 (Box 175A)
    - Album: "Morskoi Korpus v Bizerte,", undated
  - P.W. 14
    - Album: "Nashemu Vozhdiu Generalu Baronu P.N. Vrangeliu Bezzavetno predannyi Krymskii Kadet,", undated
      Presented to Baron P. Vrangel' by Crimean Cadets.
- INCREMENT, 1920-1921 (Box 176)
  Increment has not been microfilmed. Razviei gore v Golom polie: handwritten journal published by the Cavalry Division interned on the Gallipoli Peninsula.
  Развѣй горе в Голомъ полѣ.- Галлиполи, Лагерь Кавалерийской дивизии. Ред. Полк. А.Я. Козинец. «Журнал основан 16 ноября 1920».
  Holdings: Без №, б.д., №1 (б.д.), 2 (б.д.), 3 (1 янв. 1921), 4 (23 янв. 1921), 8 (б.д.), 10 (29 марта 1921 – «Юбилейный»), 11 (31 марта 1921), 14 (1 мая 1921), 16 (3 июля 1921)